This is Harish Yapt Ts Him Harish's life was
absolutely barren,
absolutely
boneless Fate always betrayed him
So he didn't give a [ __ ]
Despite working hard he got less than he wanted
Poor
[Music]
Harish Obstacles and difficulties at every turn And on top of that
his
naivety Every time every opportunity slips away
Everyone curses him, taunts him, hits him with a
stapler
Even the birds around snatch his rights I mean
the whole damn
right With his hag-like face he just keeps
wandering around After going through this [ __ ] When
his heart wants entertainment Then
yours is like
[Music]
Ugly
Then he looked at his laptop And for the first
time apart from pun
[Music]
After years a smile appeared on his face
Comedy Factory's screen
changed his world
Even the opinions started to seem like his own
[Music]
Then he came to know about the first ever
Gujarat Comedy Festival Where
all the comedians from big comedians to legends are going to
perform For the first
time Harish completed a task without any hindrance
Booked the  Tickets of the Gujarat
Comedy Festival on Book My Show He is
Happy He will be Happier Be Like Harish Come
to the Gujarat Comedy Festival Curated
by The Comedy Factory and The Idea Bag
Inc We Guarantee You Big Love Tickets on Book
My Show Did We Mention Book My Show Or I Guess
We Did For More Details Call
9898 2349 and 9879
1398 Book Your Tickets for the Gujarat Comedy
Festival on Book My Show Tickets on Book My
Show O I Already Mention That